Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: History and Politics
  - Subseries C: Chinese Americans
    - San Francisco Anti-Chinese Ordinances 1850-1900, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Food Habits of Nineteenth-century California Chinese - by Robert F.G. Spier, March 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - California Historical Society Quarterly, June 1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "The Images of China and the Chinese in the Overland Monthly", 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - [Quotations from Chairman Mao Tse-Tung, "Statement by Comrade Mao Tse-Tung...in support of the Afro-American Struggle against Violent Repression"], 1966, 1968, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "The Chinese Community in Los Angeles" in Social Casework, December 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Chinese in San Francisco Employment Problems, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Peking Review 18, April 30, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "China in New York" vol. 1, no. 1, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Cathay in Eldorado: The Chinese in California, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Chinese Historical Society of America, vol. VIII, no. 1, January 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Chinese Historical Society of Americal Bulletin (1 of 6), Febuary 1973-December 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - The China Trade by K.H.J. Clarke, September 20, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Three Generations of Chinese - East and West" - The Oakland Museum, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Chinese Historical Society of Americal Bulletin (2 of 6), January 1975-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "The Chinese American: Inscrutable to Some", 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - [Chinese Historical Society of America conference on "The Life, Influence, and the Role of the Chinese in the United States, 1776-1960"], July 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Chinese Historical Society of Americal Bulletin (3 of 6), January 1977-December 1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Gum Saan Journal, Chinese Historical Society of Southern California, August 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Chinese Pioneers, February 1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "The Chinese Historical Society of America Presents Journeys Made...Journeys to Come" - announcement, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - New China, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Chinese and the Gold Rush: Slave trading, murder, prejudice, untold hardships faced thousands of Chinese emigrating to California during the late 1800's", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Chinese Historical Society of Americal Bulletin (4 of 6), January 1979-April 1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Chinese Historical Society of Americal Bulletin (5 of 6), May 1980-May/June 1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Chinese Historical Society of Americal Bulletin (6 of 6), September 1982-June 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Chinese American Art News, vols. 15, 16, 17, November 1990-July 1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Dealing with Chinese, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Lin Yutang: Pioneer of Chinese-American Literature, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Race Traitor: Treason to whiteness is Loyalty to Humanity, no. 15, Fall 2001 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - "The Chinese in California", 2004 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - [Anna May Wong Ephemera], Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - "A Capsule Story of the Chinese Historical Society of America in San Francisco's Chinatown", Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Chinese Telegraphic code manual, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Images of Chinese, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - "A New Light on the Chinese" article in Harper's New Weekly, Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Images of Chinese [Flat Box], Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Subseries D: Chinatowns
    - "Chinatown Declared a Nuisance" essay, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - "Slumming in New York's Chinatown" by William Maloney, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A Bit of Old China, by Charles W. Stoddard, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "The Street of Dragon Lanterns, Chinatown - San Francisco" by C.F. Hobby, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Ling Long Museum (The Highlights of Chinese History) and Chicago's Chinatown", 1935 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "Chinatown Report 1969" by the Chinatown Study Group, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - New York Chinatown Education Project, revised proposal, July 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "The Elderly Chinese of the Community, Their Problems and Services Provided to Them" by Agnes Poon, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Chinatown Wax Museum - souvenir guidebook, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Chinatown community planning workshop program, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - "New York Chinatown History Project Workshop, with Silk Wings: Asian American Women at Work", May 6, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Who's Who in Chinatowns of Greater New York", 1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - 11 Interviews on Why Chinatown Youths Join Gangs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Arnold Genthe photos of Chinatown (1 of 2), Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Arnold Genthe photos of Chinatown (2 of 2), Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Arnold Genthe photos - photocopies, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "A Bright Spot in Chinatown", Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Chinatown: A View from Within" photo exhibit card, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Chinatown after Dark, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "Chinatown Health Studies Project" by the Basement Workshop, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Chinatown postcards, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "Guide to Chinatown", Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - [H.C. Noll's Official Trip to Chinatown], Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - "In Quest of Chinatown", Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "Statistics of the Chinatown Health Fair", Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Touring China Town, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Voice of Chinatown, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Subseries E: Japanese Americans
    - "Japanese in the City of San Francisco" - Roosevelt, December 1906 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - "Discrimination against Japanese in California" by Herbert B. Johnson, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - [1- Film still, "The Chinese Parrot", The Museum of Modern Art; 2- "The White Man" vol.1, no.1, June 1910; 3- Original folder], 1910, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - "California's Plea to America" by John S. Chambers, May 1921 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - "Japanese Immigration and Colonization" by V.S. McClatchy, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - "Japanese Immigration" by Raymond Leslie Buell, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Totalizer; Fighting Americans, Too, September 12, 1942; Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - "Democracy and Japanese Americans" by Norman Thomas, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - "A Social Study of the Japanese Population in the Greater New York Area", 1942 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Minutes - Japanese American Citizens League - Special emergency national conference, January 1, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Supplement to minutes - Japanese American Citizens League - Special emergency national conference, January 1, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Public auction sale catalogue of the liquidation of the Reference Library of Yamanaka Co. & Inc..., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - "What About Our Japanese Americans?" by Carey McWilliams, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - American Japanese Sightseeing Coloring and Talking Book, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Influences of Emigrants on their Home Village, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - "Nikkei Amerikajin of Hawaii", 1956 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - "My Fifty Years in America" by P.M. Suski, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Invitation to Reception for the Prince and Princess of Japan, September 8, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - "Executive Order 9066" pamphlet; "California Librarian" vol. XXXI, no. 3, July 1970, July 1970; Undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Japanese in America, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - "Pioneer Center Annual" - Japanese Community Pioneer Center, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - "The Lost Years, 1942-46", 1972 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Pamphlet on Japanese Internment - Asian American Alliance, Oberlin College, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - The American Foundation Newsletter - various volumes, April 1978-January 2002 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - "Chinatown - a thriving community with problems" in Neighborhood: The Journal for City Preservation, December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - "The World War II Incarceration on Japanese Americans and the Struggle for Reparations / Redress", November 1980 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - "Fishmerchant's Daughter" by Yuri Kochiyama, November 1981 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - "Nisei Week" flyers and calendar, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - "Redress Legislative Handbook, 98th Congress" - Japanese American Citizens League, National Committee for Redress, January 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - National Council for Japanese Redress Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "A Gathering for World Peace", 1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - National Japanese American Historical Society Calendar, Nikkei Music Makers: The Swing Era, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Nikkei Heritage" vol. VII, no. 2, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The National Japanese American Memorial Foundation Newsletter, October 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Nanking Massacre - book, pamphlet, and form letter, 1997, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Questionnaire, Japanese Language Consciousness of Americans - Hirosaki University, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - "The Legacy of Silence: A Japanese American Story" - an exhibition at the UC Irvine Library, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - National Diet Library Newsletter, February 2005 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Japanese American Social Services, Inc - newsletter, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "Against All Odds: The Campaign in Congress for Japanese American Redress" - Harvard University, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Better in a Greater America, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Book reproducing Yoriko Watanabe Sasaki's collection of newspaper clippings related to Japanese internment, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - The Draft and You, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - "An Ecological Study of the Japanese in New York City", Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "The Experience of Japanese Ameicans in the United States: A Teacher Resource Manual", Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - The Grafton Peace Pagoda call for volunteers, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - James D. Phelan campaign advertisement, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Japanese American United Church publication, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Japanese Viewpoints: Expressions in Fiction, Poetry, Drama, Thought, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - "Nikkei Sentinal", Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "Please Don't" - Japanese American Citizens League brochure, Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Wakamatsu Colony Sentinal, JACL, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Japanese Propogandy posters - magazine cutout [Flat Box], Undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Subseries F: Asians and Asian Americans
    - The North American Review, vol CXXXIV, 1882 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - The First Japanese Embassy, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Californians of Japanese, Chinese, Filipino Ancestry, June 1965 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - "Building Bridges of Understanding Between Cultures" pamphlet, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - "Asian Americans for Action" - Abrogate US-Japan Security Treaty, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Demonstration for China to have a U.N. seat - flyer, September 1971 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - "The Women's American-Oriental Club of New York City, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Church Women United - Asian Americans packet, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - "Criminal Intelligence Bulletin" - California Department of Justice, July 1973 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - AAC Newsletter, no. 2, October 1973 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Asian American Coalition Newsletter, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Mid-Atlantic Conference on Community Concerns of Asian Americans - program, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - A Dream Unfulfilled: Korean and Filipino Health Professionals in California, May 1975 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Statement of Franklin H. Williams[...] on 'The Forgotten Minority: A Review of Problems Confronting Asian Americans in New York City', May 27, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - "CAAW" vol. I, no. 1-3, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - "Honolulu Residents and Thier Attitudes in Multi-Ethnic Perspective: Toward a Theory of the American National Characte", February 1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - The Asian American Journey, September 1980 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Letter Accompanying Review copy of "The Year of the Monkey", 1988 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Asian Business and Community News, vol. 7, no. 6, June 1989 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - "Final Copy: the Monthly Newsletter of the Asian American Jounalists Association - New York chapter", December 1989 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Current Asian, vol. IV, no. 3, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Asian American Federation of New York, NEWS, April 1992 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Pacific / Asian Affairsm vol. I, no.1, August 1992 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - "Onoto Watanna's Japanese Nightingale Dissected: Images of the Japanese Women in Turn-of-the-Century American" by Mariko Deborah Maeda, May 15, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - "WoFat's Incomplete Cultural Guide - Asian Gangs Symposium", June 1993 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - 14th Asian / Pacific American Heritage Festival, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - "New, New York", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - 1995 AAAS National Conference (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - A/AC News: Emergency Edition - vol. 2, no. 2, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Asian American studies materials from Cornell University, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - "Asian Women in Business" vol. I, issue I, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - "explanAsian: the Publication of the Asian American Writer's Workshop" vol. I, no. 4, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - The Korea Society calendar of events May-June 1996 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Program for the 13th National Conference of the Association for Asian American Studies, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Homage Au Vietnam: A Celebration, March 1997 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Fifteenth Annual Meeting of the Association for Asian Amrican Studies - conference brochure, June 1998 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - PoliticalCircus.com newsletter, May 2001 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - CAAAV Voice - vol. 11, no. 1; vol. 14, no. 1; vol. 15, no. 2, 2002, 2006, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - "Cross Currents" vol. 26, no. 2; vol. 27, no. 1; vol. 29, no. 2, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - A Brief History of U.S. Asian Labor, Undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Godzilla: the Asian American Arts Network, Undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Images of Asians, Undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Pacific / Asian Elderly Resource Center Development Project, Undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Photo of Asian family - from Dr. Hsieh, Justice of the Peace, Undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Saturday Night at the Pahala Theater, by Lois-Ann Yamanaka, Undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Sheet music (1 of 2), Undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Sheet Music (2 of 2), Undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Sheet music - photocopies of cover pages, Undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Southeast Asian Folk Art Festival, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - United Asian Community Center, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - "What Does it Take to be the Best" Hofstra University ad from NY Times Magazine [Flat Box], 1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Series III: Curricular Studies
  This series contains bibliographies, reports, teaching guides, resource packets, syllabi, and periodicals which were used to support or discuss Asian American and diversity studies.
  - Subseries A: Asian American Studies
    - Asian American Center, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Center - grant application, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Asian American Studies" binder (1 of 6), 1970-1973, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "Asian American Studies" binder (2 of 6), 1970-1972, 1974, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Asian American Studies" binder (3 of 6), 1969, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Asian American Studies" binder (4 of 6), 1970, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - "Asian American Studies" binder (5 of 6), 1970, 1971, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - "Asian American Studies" binder (6 of 6), 1971, 1974, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Asian American Studies courses - bibliographies, 1970, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Asian American Studies course handouts and syllabi, A-H, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Asian American Studies handouts and syllabi, I-O, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Asian American Studies handouts and syllabi, P-X, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - "Asian Americans: a Guide to publications for young readers", Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Asian / Pacific / American Studies - Fall 1997 courses (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - The Association for Asian American Studies call for papers, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholards (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - The Bobbs-Merrill Reprint series in the social sciences, 1928, 1945, 1949, 1956, 1964, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "CommunicAsians: Asian Involvement at Stanford", Winter 2003 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Cross Currents: News Magazine of the UCLA Asian American Studies Center, 2005-2006, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Ethnic Heritage Studies program, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ethnic Studies Interim Conference 1971 Report (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Copies of images used in Smithsonian lecture, Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Media - book list, Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - "Milton K. Ozaki: An Asian American Mystery", 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Queens College - grant application for Asian American center, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Scrutable Images Lecture, Smithsonian, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - "Shiel in Diverse Hands: a Collection of Essays" (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - "Shiel in Diverse Hands: a Collection of Essays" (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - "A Syllabus: The Japanese American in the United States", June 1969 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Subseries B: Diversity in Education
    - "Aids to Media Selection for Students and Teachers" and supplement, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - American Diversity: A Bibliography of Resources on Racial and Ethnic Minorities for Pennsylvania Schools, 1971, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - "Asia in American Textbooks: An Evaluation" by the Asia Society, Inc., March 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Asian American People and Places - Ethnic Understanding Series, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - "China in American School Textbooks" by Timothy Lew, July 1923 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Chinese Americans Past and Present: a collection of Chinese American readings and learning activities", 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars Education packet, June 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Ideas for Young Children, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Education Concerns of Asian and Pacific Americans, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Education: The Dilemma of the Oriental-American" by George L. Farmer, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - ERIC Clearinghouse for Social Studies / Social Sciences Education - Interpretive series nos. 5 and 6, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - ERIC Report - "Chinese American Identity and Children's Picture Books", January 1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - ERIC Report - "Task Force to Reevaluate Social Science Textbooks Grades Five through Eight", December 1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - FOCUS on Asian Studies: A Newsletter to Promote Increased Attention to Asian Studiesin Elementary and Secondary Education, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Foreign Studies: Teacher's Guide", 1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - A Guide to the Analysis of Schoolbook Content: Evaluating Print Materials from a Chinese American Perspective, October 1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Guidelines for Textbook Selection: The treatment of Minorities, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - "Students, Teachers abd the Third World in the American College Curriculum", 1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Mid-Atlantic Directory to Resources for Asian Studies, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Multicultural workshop resource packet on Asian Americans, August 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - One-Third of a Nation: A Report of the Comission on Minority Participation in Education and American Life, May 1988 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - A Report to Educators on Teaching Films survey, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - A Syllabus of Chinese Civilization, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - A syllabus of the history of Chinese civilization and culture, 4th edition, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - A Teacher's Guide for an Illustrated History of the Chinese in America, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Teacher's Manual: Passage to the Golden Gate, by Daniel Chu and Samuel Chu, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Teaching Tolerance, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Topics in Culture Learning, vol. 1-3, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Topics in Culture Learning, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - "Treatment of Asian in American Textbooks", 1946 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - "Unity: an Asian Studies Reading Kit" Longfellow School, Berkeley, California, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - What is Filipino?, January 1977 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Series IV: Hollywood Films, Television, Theater, and Actors
  This series contains periodicals, clippings, photocopied articles, photos, movie posters, film stills, headshots, and promotional material for Asian American actors, and for films and theater with Asian American themes or characters.
  - Subseries A: Film
    - 20th Asian American International Film Festival, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 21st Annual American Film Festival program, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Amerasia: a Prospectus - submitted to the Educational Film Center, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - American Cinematographer - magazine, 1980, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - American Film - magazine, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - American Film - magazine, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "American Indians in Silent Film", 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "American Indians on Film and Video", 1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "An Analysis of Asian American Stereotypes on the American Screen" by Li Ping Lee, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Film Fest program, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - "Asian Americans: The East in the West" materials, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - The Asian Image in the United States, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - "Asia Through Film", 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Benten Kozo, Revenge of the Geisha - announcement cards, 1999, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Binder - "1 to 1894" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Binder - "1 to 1894" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Binder - "3 1895", Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Binder - "4", Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Binder - "5 1908", Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Binder - "5" (loose material), Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Binder - "6", Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Binder - "7 1914", Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Binder - "8 1917" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Binder - "8 1917" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Binder - "9; 10 Tsuru Aoki", Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Binder - "11 1918" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Binder - "11 1918" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Binder - "12" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Binder - "12" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Binder - "13", Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Binder - "14A SH 1919-1922", Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Binder - "14 SH 1914-1918", Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Binder - "15 1923", Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Binder - "16 1925", Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Binder - "17; 18 1928", Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)